# Ryan Jonah

# Software Developer

With a lifelong passion for technology and years of experience assisting customers through a myriad of different issues, this dedicated problem solver is willing to face every new prospect with an adamant determination towards finding solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance, Moncton, NB— Software Developer

September 2021 - Present

• I am currently building a website for Whispering Willow; a wedding venue located in south-eastern New Brunswick.

## **Cloud5**, Minto, NB— Customer Service Representative

January 2017 - August 2020 January 2014 - February 2015

- Selling, creating, and canceling hotel reservations across multiple accounts covering hundreds of properties internationally.
- Helping customers resolve issues via phone and email by way of information gathering, internal systems processing, reviewing hotel and company policies, and consulting hotel staff directly.
- Assisting customers with billing inquiries while following Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance.
- Assisting other call center representatives through escalation calls while fulfilling the rotational role of shift supervisor.
- Assisting customers through the navigation of various hotel websites.
- Assisting other call center representatives in troubleshooting technical issues.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **NBCC,** Moncton, NB— Web and Mobile Application Development

September 2020 - June 2021

**Coder Foundry**, Kernersville, NC— Coding Bootcamp

June 2021 - September 2021

Gagetown,
New Brunswick
(506) 327-5298
ryan c jonah@yahoo.ca

Portfolio LinkedIn Github

#### **SKILLS**

C#

ASP.NET

**Entity Framework** 

HTML

**CSS** 

Javascript

Bootstrap

React

Git

Python

LINQ

MS SQL Server

Windows OS

Linux OS

Bash

**Customer Service** 

Sales

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

#### **Hobbies**

Technology, fitness, writing, philosophy, science, history, music, cooking, video games